let questions = [    {   
       numb: 1, 
              question: '1.Which of this method we use for debugging or testing code in JavaScript ?',        
              answer: 'console.log()',      
                options: [         
                    "document.Write()",       
                         "innerHTML",         
                            "console.log()",  
                                   "window.alert()"        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 2,
        question: "2.Which of these data types is not a primitive data type?",
        answer: 'Object',
        options: [
          "Undefined",
          "Object",
          "Boolean",
          "Number"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 3,
        question: "3.What is the result of 2 + '2' in JavaScript?",
        answer: '22',
        options: [
          "4",
          "22",
          "NaN",
          "TypeError"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 4,
        question: "4.What is the correct way to define a JavaScript function?",
        answer: 'function myFunction() {}',
        options: [
          "myFunction = function() {}",
          "function = myFunction() {}",
          "function myFunction() {}",
          "myFunction() = function() {}"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 5,
        question: "5.What is the output of the following code in JavaScript? 'hello'.indexOf('l')",
        answer: '2',
        options: [
          "1",
          "2",
          "3",
          "4"
        ]
    },
    {
      numb: 6,
      question: "6.What is the output of the following code? console.log(typeof null);",
      answer: "object",
      options: [
        "null",
        "undefined",
        "object",
        "number"
      ]
    },
    {
      numb: 7,
      question: "7.What is the purpose of JavaScript closures?",
      answer: "To access variables outside a function.",
      options: [
        "To hide code from view.",
        "To generate random numbers.",
        "To validate form input.",
        "To access variables outside a function."
      ]
    },
    {
      numb: 8,
      question: "8.What is the output of the following code? console.log(5 + '5');",
      answer: "55",
      options: [
        "10",
        "55",
        "NaN",
        "undefined"
      ]
    },
    {
      numb: 9,
      question: "9.Which keyword is used to declare a variable in JavaScript?",
      answer: "var",
      options: [
        "let",
        "const",
        "var",
        "variable"
      ]
    },
    {
      numb: 10,
      question: "10.Which of the following is a JavaScript framework/library?",
      answer: "React",
      options: [
        "Java",
        "Python",
        "C++",
        "React"
      ]
    },
];
